[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Illinois, the 21st US State?", "correct_answer": "Springfield", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago", "Lincoln", "Omaha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many balls are on the snooker table at the beginning of the game?", "correct_answer": "22", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "15", "19"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can skunks be trained to make good pets?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was called Big Train. He was the first baseball player whose last name began with a J to be elected to the Baseball Hall of Fame. Who was he?", "correct_answer": "Walter Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Judy Johnson", "Ban Johnson", "Addie Joss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This U.S. general, born in Little Rock Arkansas, fought in 3 major wars (World War I, World War II, Korean War) and was one of the few men ever to rise to the rank of General of the Army.", "correct_answer": "Douglas MacArthur", "incorrect_answers": ["Omar Bradley", "Dwight Eisenhower", "Colin Powell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food should be at least partly prepared by Jews to be considered suitable for consumption according to Jewish laws?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Bread", "Wine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "They are nocturnal.", "incorrect_answers": ["They live in and out of the water.", "They are poisonous.", "Their lifecycle is divided into three stages."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first actor of Latino-American heritage to win an Academy Award?", "correct_answer": "Rita Moreno", "incorrect_answers": ["Anthony Quinn", "Henry Silva", "Guilliermo Hernandez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie features With great power comes great responsibility. as a tag line?", "correct_answer": "Spider-Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Dare Devil", "Superman", "Batman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It doesnt matter if the guy is perfect or the girl is perfect, as long as they are perfect for each other. (1997)", "correct_answer": "Good Will Hunting", "incorrect_answers": ["Forest Gump", "The Shawshank Redemption", "Citizen Kane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1927 movie Wings was the first winner of the Best Picture Oscar. Which of these actors was in it?", "correct_answer": "Gary Cooper", "incorrect_answers": ["Ray Milland", "Brian Donleavy", "Charlie Chaplin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a town in Oklahoma called IXL.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]